drivertoolkit.com 2018-12-18

# DriverToolkit - Privacy Policy

## Privacy Statement

Megaify Software (hereinafter, "Megaify") is committed to protecting your privacy. Please read the Megaify Online Privacy Statement below and also any supplemental information listed to the right for extra details about particular Megaify sites and services that you may use.

This Megaify Online privacy Statement applies to data collected by Megaify through the majority of its Websites and services, as well as its offline product customer support. It does not apply to those Megaify sites, services and products that do not show or link to this statement or that have their own privacy statements.

#### 1\. Collecting Personal Information

If you have ordered our product(s), in order to save your purchase information, your name and email will be save to our user database. We may collect information about your visit, such as the pages you view, the hyperlinks you click and other actions taken in connection with Megaify sites and services. We also collect certain standard information that your web browser sends to every website you visit, including your ip address, browser name and language, access times and referring Website locations. To be able to offer you a more consistent and customized experience in your interactions with Megaify, information collected through one Megaify service may be combined with information obtained through other Megaify services.

#### 2\. Using of Personal Information

Megaify collects and uses your personal information to operate and promote its websites and deliver the services or perform the transactions you have requested. These uses may include providing you with more proficient customer service; which makes the websites or services easier to use by reducing the need for you to routinely enter the same information; carrying out analysis and research focused at improving our products, services and technologies; and showing content and advertising that are customized to your preferences. We also use your personal information to interact with you. We may send certain mandatory service communications such as registration confirmation, billing reminders, technical service information, and security notices. Personal information collected on Megaify sites and services may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Megaify or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using a Megaify website or service, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. Megaify abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European.

#### 3\. Security of Personal Information

Megaify is committed to securing your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to prevent your personal information from illegal access. E.g., we hold the personal information you provide on computers with limited access, which are located in controlled environments. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number or password) over the Internet, we secure it with the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

#### 4\. Enforcement

Megaify regularly reviews its compliance with this statement. Please contacting us if you have any concerns or questions about this policy or Megaify's treatment of personal information. When we receive formal complaints at this address, it is Megaify's procedure to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal information that cannot be resolved between Megaify and an individual. We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. We encourage you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how Megaify is safeguarding your personal information.

#### 5\. Contacting Us

Megaify welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement. If you have questions about this statement or feel that we have not honored it, please contact US.
